http://www.videoguys.com/policies/privacy-policy

FREE Shipping on All orders in the Continental US... Plus Free tech advice & support at 800-323-2325
HomeHoliday SpecialsCatalog
Live Production SystemsStreaming EncodersNDI ProductsPTZ Cameras & ControllersStorage SolutionsConvertersAudioBrands
AngelBirdAtomosAvidBirdDogBoris FXEpiphanFXHOMEG-TechnologyGlyph Production TechnologiesGrass ValleyHuddleCamLacieLiveUMAGIXMatroxmLogicNewBlueNewTekPanasonicProGrade DigitalPioneerPTZOpticsRed GiantRolandSandiskSecureDataSimplyLiveSlingStudioSmallHDTelestreamTeradekWowzaXKEYSYoloLivArticlesVideoguys LIVE!
Privacy policy
For more than 30 years, Videoguys.com / The Electronic Mailbox / TEM Trading Inc. has worked hard to build relationships with our customers based on respect and integrity. We're aware of the trust and confidence you demonstrate when you visit our website and provide us with information. We promise that we will treat your information with the same honesty and sensitivity that we have displayed throughout our company's history.Our goal has always been to provide the best customer service and support in the industry. In addition to our 30-day money back guarantee and availability to free tech support we are constantly utilizing new technology to better meet your needs. Some of these new features like the monthly e-newsletters and the Videoguys' Forums require your personal information. After all, we couldn't e-mail you the latest news without your e-mail address and it's nice to read a post from someone who has an identity. Another obvious time when you will be asked to share your personal information is when you are ready to place an order in which case billing, shipping and financial information must be collected to fulfill your request. The question this privacy policy addresses is "What will we do with that information?"We will NEVER share your financial information with anyone other the banks whose authorization is necessary to approve the order. Every credit card number provided to our company will be treated as if it was our own whether it is provided over the phone or by using our secure online order system. Our website protects the security of your personal information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We do not reveal your credit card number when we confirm your order.When you place your order and/or when you request that we send you information we may share your name and mailing address with a few carefully selected marketing partners. We may also provide some of our vendors with your contact information so that they may contact you directly for product support, tech bulletins and upgrade information. This is a great way to make sure you are getting the most from your purchase and your relationship with us. If you would prefer that we do not share the information just tell your salesperson or complete any of the simple unsubscribe requests included with every correspondence.If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy please call us toll-free at:1-800-323-2325; e-mail us at videoguy@videoguys.com; or send a letter to: Videoguys, 179 Liberty Ave, Mineola NY 11501.This privacy policy sets out how Video Guys uses and protects any information that you give Videoguys when you use this website. Videoguys is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Videoguys may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.What we collectWe may collect the following information:
Name
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How we use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at custserv@videoguys.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 179 Liberty Ave, Mineola NY 11501.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.List of cookies we collectThe list below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
CART The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED The items that you have recently compared.
STF Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT The number of items in your Wishlist.
FREE U.S. Shipping
FREE ground delivery on all orders in the Continental U.S. with expedited shipping available
30-day Money Back Guarantee
Our goal is to make sure you are 100% satisfied with your purchase
FREE Tech Advice & Support
Call us at 800-323-2325 to speak with a live person who can help you before or after your purchase
Secure payments
Videoguys.com proudly accepts all major U.S. credit cards and will protect your safety & security
